Hey.
Are you a first-year?
Who's asking?
This isn't a parking lot,
so maybe you should
park that somewhere else.
Shouldn't she tell me not to
ride a motorbike to school?
What an odd upperclassman.
Students weren't allowed to
ride motorbikes to school.
My buddy told me
the lot behind the old club building
was a great place to hide one.
We found something behind
the old club building.
If anyone knows what
I'm talking about, come forward.
As luck would have it, I parked my bike
somewhere else that day.
By the end of class, the teachers
had apparently found the hiding spot.
Don't speak to me again.
Yeah, got it.
I wasn't stupid or a troublemaker.
The girls kind of liked me,
so I tried my luck.
That stings...
Didn't go as well as the last
girl you talked to, did it?
Got a minute?
These boxes for the student
council aren't heavy,
but there are too many to carry at once.
So you're on the student council?
You could say that.
But I mostly do grunt work.
This is too much for one person to carry.
How many trips have you made?
Everyone has to do their part.
Sengoku-kun!
Koyanagi-san.
It's about time. This is
a time-sensitive matter.
Any delay on your end delays everyone.
Oh my...
Looks like they're all here. Good work.
I said good work. You can go now.
Is there something else?
You made a girl lug all those boxes here
and all you can say is "good work,"
Mr. Student Council President?
How about a thank you?
What class are you from?
Class 1-9.
I'm Hori Kyosuke.
I'm Sengoku Takeru, class 3-1.
Wear your uniform properly, first-year.
And also...
Thank you, Koyanagi-san.
Sorry for butting in like that.
What do you mean?
I didn't think that it might make
things awkward with the student council.
If it got awkward, I'd just quit.
Huh, she's pretty easygoing.
Um, Koyanagi-san...
Koyanagi Yuriko.
I should have introduced myself sooner.
Yuriko...
Koyanagi Yuriko...
I went to a dog café and saw
a dog that looked just like you!
They say a person's name
captures who they are.
For real? Must've been one good-looking dog.
And I thought...
she looked just like the lily in hers
when she smiled.
Koyanagi-san, what are you
gonna do after graduation?
I haven't really decided.
What about you, Hori-kun?
Me?
I mean, I don't really know.
That's how it goes.
Say, Koyanagi-san...
Once you graduate...
Even after you graduate...
Nah, forget I said that.
Oh?
I feared crushing
the flower I held in my hand.
What's Kyosuke to you?
He's head over heels for a third-year,
but you're not even pretty.
Okay...
Are you even listening?!
Hurry up and graduate already
so you can get your ass away from him!
Yuriko!
Oh.
Kyosuke!
What are you doing to Yuriko?!
Stay out of it! This is between me and her!
You...
Kyosuke, stop.
A man should never
raise a hand against a woman.
Oh, but that doesn't apply to me.
I'm a woman, after all.
She was as gentle as a flower,
but this lily...
had thorns.
That's when I knew she was the one.
Sting
I see.
Listen, you should think of her slap
as a sign of affection.
I'll try.
So, why'd she slap you?
Huh? I don't remember...
Yeah, that happens sometimes.
Well, Kyoko can be dangerous
once she gets angry, so be careful.
I see...
Kyosuke-san!
Huh? What is it, Miyamura-kun?
It suddenly started hurting a lot more!
Throb...
Really?!
So that happens to you, too?!
Ow... Ow... Ow, ow, ow!
What?! It hurts... Why?! Ouch!
Suck it up!
Don't give in, Miyamura-kun!
The Hori House
Kyosuke, I need to borrow a shirt.
A t-shirt will do.
Why? Are you gonna use it as a rag?
No. All the shirts I use after
a bath are in the laundry, so...
I don't have any cute ones.
If you handed me a cute one,
I wouldn't take it.
As long as you don't mind one
that's way too big for you...
Not like I have a choice.
Big Sis, look!
Mama bought this for me!
N-Nice.
It floats, really! It floats in water!
Lift
Vengeful spirit!
Squeeze
Vengeful spirit?!
Did you mean to say "vicious beast"?
What's this, Kyoko?
Have you developed...
a brother composite?!
"Composite"? Do you mean a brother complex?
And no! I was just wondering
if Sota's clothes would fit me!
Probably too small.
You ate a ton of mochi
over New Year's, remember?
Wh-What?!
Are you saying I'm fat?!
No, I wouldn't go that far—
Same difference, idiot!
Oh my.
It'll fit, and I'll prove it!
Sota, get me a t-shirt!
Huh? I don't want to.
Fine, then I'll go get it!
Rrring
Can I call Miyamura-kun?
Do whatever you want!
It's an ordinary day,
but things are still so fun.
Hey, Miyamura-kun, are you free?
We're doing HFW here.
HFW.
HFW?
What, Miyamura-kun?
You've never heard of HFW?
Well, today's actually the first ever.
Ah, swapping "Hori" for "Paris" in PFW.
Well?! See?!
It fits just fine!
A hoodie is cheating, don't you think?
They're meant to be big.
What's really surprising is how tight
clothes make your chest look bigger.
Shut up! You're the worst!
But...
High schoolers normally can't wear
elementary schooler's clothes.
They leave things unsaid
Can you get that, Kyosuke?
He won't be able to argue with this!
See? It fits just fine!
Oh, it's Sota's shirt.
SNAP
Shock
Wh-Wh-What's he doing here?
You told me to do whatever I wanted.
No, I didn't!
Ah, I'm so embarrassed!
Your belly button's showing.
That must be cold.
Comment
Kyoko, he says your flap is hanging out.
Big Sis, what part of the cow is flap meat?
Shut up!
The Hori house is always so much fun.
I'm not having any fun.
I ate too much mochi and gained weight.
Girls really worry about their weight, huh?
So why were you having a fashion show?
Good question.
I was going to borrow
a shirt from Kyosuke...
Kyoko turned into a vicious beast.
Or, wait, maybe it was a vengeful spirit.
Comment
But she was just trying to borrow a shirt.
Big Sis, is our house haunted?!
Comment
Shut up!
You're the loudest of all
when you shout like that, Kyoko.
You're the one making stupid comments!
Miyamura-kun, you're
staying for dinner, right?
Oh, so it's my fault?
Oh, yes, thank you.
Why do you always try to blame me?
You'll end up a delinquent.
Let's eat before it gets cold.
Okay!
You saying that at your age
when you're the root of all evil!
Your life needs a do-over!
Even if I do it over, I'll still be your father!
I'm never giving that up! You can rest easy!
No, I can't!
That's what freaks me out!
The Hori house really is fun.
Sota!
You made a mess again!
I was just about to clean it up.
I've heard that before!
It's true!
You always leave your messes behind.
No, I don't!
Grit
Hey, hey, what are you so angry about?
Sota leaves his stuff all over the place.
No! I was about to clean up,
but then she started yelling!
You heard him.
Oh, so you're on his side, eh?
I-I made some tea. Maybe we could...
Listen!
Listen to this!
Um, okay... I'll hear you out.
Let's just sit down first.
Um...
Sota's been doing a good job
of cleaning up lately.
Maybe he just left his stuff out today.
You get too angry!
Way too angry!
Hmph...
Poke, poke.
Poke
Kyoko, I'm on your side.
Kyosuke...
I've always wondered why you
jump the gun when you get angry.
It's more than just being
short-tempered. Are you okay?
Kyosuke-san!
Now she's run off!
I asked you not to upset her!
I didn't mean it!
Big Sis!
Kyoko, remember that I'm on your side!
Come on out!
Open...
Oh, there she is.
Kyoko—
Don't touch me.
Big Sis—
Hori-san—
Don't touch me.
What's this about not touching her?
Dunno. Maybe it's her way
of letting us know that she's angry.
SEETHE...
Whoa, he's cleaning up!
Shuffle Shuffle
Sota's cleaning up, Hori-san!
Sota can come through when—
Don't touch me.
Slap!!
Hori-san!
Don't touch me.
Slap!!
What's going on, Miyamura-kun?!
It looks bleak.
We need to calm her down little by little.
Hori-san, want some pudding?
I've given it up.
Kyoko-chan, should I rub your shoulders?
Don't touch me.
Kyoko—
Really?
We're in outer space!
What are you talking about?
This is our house.
H-Hori-san...
This is outer space and we're in a spaceship!
SHOVE
I'm trying to study, okay?
If you go outside, you'll die!
SHOVE
Space sounds like fun!
I wouldn't mind going!
Don't close your notebooks!
Don't put away your textbooks!
If you leave this area,
you'll die 'cause there's no air.
Where did you even find this old carpet?
We're gonna build a villa on the moon!
Sounds good!
Push
My big sister killed me!
You will now address me as captain.
A heartless, unfeeling captain.
We're circling Mars!
Now I'm friends with this Martian!
Aw, man...
She's just taken over the ship,
and she's already recruiting
more crew members.
Just who is Hori-san?
Bis Sis!
Come on!
Hori-san, um...
Can Sota come back on the ship?
Then he'd grow into a weak man who thinks
he can just get whatever he wants.
He was the one who decided that
whoever leaves this area would die.
All I did was push him.
Squeeze
Push him
(to certain death)
What's that? A new vehicle?
Yeah. I managed to board an escape pod.
The sorrow of betrayal will
fuel my quest for revenge.
Do you even know what that means?
You can do it, Sota!
Scoot
Yeah!
There's a spy in our midst!
I'm cheering for him since
he's part of our crew!
I'll have to be a captain
who doesn't trust a single soul.
Man... this is a lot.
Take this!
Yes, I beat her!
I won, Big Bro—
Sota, run for it!
RUMBLE
The captain is immortal!
Glance...
Sota, are you doing kanji?
Yeah.
Aw, man, I wish that was my homework.
You're a third-year high schooler.
"Make a compound word
using the word 'forest.'"
Forestland.
Quick answer
Hori-san, he needs to think about it himself.
Oh!
I'm home!
Oh, Sota, you're doing homework?
Ask me for whatever you need.
You smell like cigarettes!
Not what I was expecting.
Kyosuke stinks.
Because of the cigarettes!
Don't make it sound like I stink.
Stinky.
Kicking a man while he's down...
Kanji Drills
Hori Sota
The "So" in your name is hard to write, huh?
Still, it's really impressive that
you're learning kanji in first grade.
He's supposed to, isn't he?
I couldn't write the kanji
for my given name either.
I can't do it!
Miyamura Iz
Izmi
Izui
You're such a good helper, Sota.
I hope you'll help me again.
Sure!
Sota, let's finish your homework—
What are you doing?!
Clack
I told you to let me do those!
Um, but...
No buts!
You could cut yourself on the knives.
You're a jerk!
What?
WAAAH
Shock
I told you it's dangerous
to do it on your own!
You always get angry right away!
Why don't you understand?!
What's wrong?
Like I said!
Sota was trying to...
Yeah.
And it's dangerous!
Well, Kyoko can be dangerous
once she gets angry, so be careful.
Hori-san, there's a better way to say that.
Sota was just trying to help.
He's in first grade now.
And you've washed them before, right?
Yeah.
But you understand what
your sister is saying too, don't you?
Yeah.
He gets it, Hori-san—
Huh?!
Wh-What's wrong?!
I... I just...
I should have...
Um, but what you said wasn't wrong.
It's okay.
But you...
Did you think I was angry with you?
I'm not. Really, I'm not.
Sota was just...
And you weren't wrong!
Big Sis is upset because of me!
What's going on?!
Fuss
What is this?
I don't know what to do!
Fuss
Oh, you guys look like you're having fun.
Can you step in?
What?
Sounds like a pain, so I'll pass.
I'm sorry, Hori-san.
Sota's still just a kid,
and I'm an only child.
I don't really know much about discipline.
I know you're trying
to do what's best for him.
Maybe I was too harsh.
I don't like it when you're not on my side.
Huh? But I am on your side.
Then... it's fine.
But when I think you're doing
something wrong, I'll get angry.
Smirk...
Is that a smile?
So, specifically, when you get angry...
are you gonna yell "stop it!" and smack me?
I'm not gonna smack you!
Hori is back to normal
Next time
page.13 Graduation
About my family
SMILE
My teacher liked what I wrote at school!
Hey, Mom, Sota wrote something
at school and the teacher liked it.
Oh my
Oh my!
Hey, you wrote about your family.
That's great! Let me see it.
Sure!
It's called "My Big Brother."
Stare
I'm so sorry...